

MÁRLON MEDEIROS BRUM Software Engineer

MY PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I have been working in software development for 27 years, with experience in various platforms and tools such as .NET, PHP, and more recently Python and artificial intelligence tools, as well as SQL Server and MySQL databases. I also work with systems analysis and gathering requirements directly with clients. I have also coordinated a team of developers, acting as a bridge between them and the business analysts..

Academic Background

Postgraduate PECE - Escola Politécnica USP MBA in Software Technology

Duration: 2 years – Finished in 2006

Higher education Faculdades Associadas de São Paulo Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Duration: 4 years - Finished in 2003 Escola Técnica Federal de São Paulo

Technical Degree in Data Processing Duration: 4 years – Finished in 1999

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer

High School

From May/2018 to Present

I currently work as a freelance professional, with several clients, including the São Paulo Institute of Engineering. I develop software solutions and provide consulting services using various technologies.

BASE Optimization Consulting e K12 Educação

From August 2011 to May 2018

I worked at the company BASE, which later merged with K12 Educação, where I became a partner. I developed a scheduling system for schools on the .NET platform, using an advanced optimization algorithm to find the best timetable. I also managed the system's operation and maintenance, overseeing the application on Azure.

PRODESP - Processamento de dados do estado de São Paulo From October 2005 to July 2011

I worked at PRODESP (outsourced by the company B2Br), on the process control system for the courts of justice of the state of São Paulo. I served both as a developer and as a coordinator of a development team, acting as an intermediary with the business analysts.



CONTACT

- Guarulhos São Paulo
- (11) 9 7649 6027
- marlon.brum@gmail.com



• Fluent English



- Backend Development
 - Asp.net
 - C#
 - **PHP**
 - Python
- Frontend Development
 - HTML5
 - Javascript ES6

 - Responsive Applications
- Mobile Development
 - React Native
 - Ionic
- Optimization Algorithms
- Artificial Intelligence
- Databases
 - SqlServer
 - MySQL
 - SQL query Language
- Systems Analysis

